Fair Employment Practices Commission Records on Microfilm 5662 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Region II: Correspondence (Sp-Z) (Reel 9FR)
- Region II: Active Cases (A-Z) (Reel 10FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (A) (Reel 11FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (A-Brooklyn Navy Yard 2-GR-825) (Reel 12FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (Brooklyn Navy Yard 2-GRr-826--CA) (Reel 13FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (Ce-E) (Reel 14FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (F-h) (Reel 15FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (I-Mi) (Reel 16FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (Mo-O) (Reel 17FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (P-R) (Reel 18FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases (s) (Reel 19FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases [T-United States (A-M)] (Reel 20FR)
- Region II: Closed Cases [United States (N-Z) -Z] (Reel 21FR)
- Region II: Predocketed Cases (A-C) (Reel 22FR)
- Region II: Predocketed Cases (D-Me) (Reel 23FR)
- Region II: Predocketed Cases (Mi-R) (Reel 24FR)
- Region II: Predocketed Cases (S-V) (Reel 25FR)
- Region II: Predocketed Cases (W-Z). Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 26FR)
- Region III: Misc. (Reel 27FR)
  Active cases: New Jersey (A-Z); Also Unarranged (Includes Philadelphia Rapid Transit)
- Region III: Active Cases (Reel 28FR)
  Unarranged; including Philadelphia Rapid Transit
- Region III: Closed Cases: Pittsburgh (A-Z) (Reel 29FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (A-Be) (Reel 30FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (Bl-Co) (Reel 31FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (Cr-Ea) (Reel 32FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases [Ed-Fankford Arsenal (misc. Complaints) (Reel 33FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases [Fankford Arsenal (A) - I] (Reel 34FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (J-Naval Observatory) (Reel 35FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases [Navy - Philadelphia Navy Yard (E)] (Reel 36FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases [Philadelphia Navy Yard (F) - Po] (Reel 37FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (P-Sig) (Reel 38FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (Sin - United Specialty) (Reel 39FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (united States Army Engineers - Wa) (Reel 40FR)
- Region III: Closed Cases (We-Z; Also Misc.) (Reel 41FR)
- Region IV: Administrative Files (A-Z) And Active Cases (3-425) (Reel 42FR)
- Region IV: Active Cases (426-624) (Reel 43FR)
- Region IV: Closed Cases (1-107) (Reel 44FR)
- Region IV: Closed Cases (108-215) (Reel 45FR)
- Region IV: Closed Cases (216-305) (Reel 46FR)
- Region IV: Closed Cases (306-295) (Reel 47FR)
- Region IV: Closed Cases (396-617). (Reel 48FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files (A-C) (Reel 49FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files [D - Final Disposition Reports (Cleveland, Cincinnati)] (Reel 50FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files [Final Disposition Reports (Detroit) - M] (Reel 51FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files (N-T) (Reel 52FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files (U-Z) (Reel 53FR)
- Region V: Administrative Files, Cincinnati (A-Z) And Active Cases, Detroit (A-F) (Reel 54FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Active Cases (G-S) (Reel 55FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Active Cases (T-Z) And Cleveland: Active Cases (A-F) (Reel 56FR)
- Region V: Cleveland: Active Cases (G-Z) And Cincinnati: Active Cases (A-F) (Reel 57FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Closed Cases (A-Che) (Reel 58FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Closed Cases (Ch-F) (Reel 59FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Closed Cases (G-Mi) (Reel 60FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Closed Cases (Mo-S) (Reel 61FR)
- Region V: Detroit: Closed Cases (T-Z) (Reel 62FR)
- Region V: Cleveland: Closed Cases (A-D) (Reel 63FR)
- Region V: Cleveland: Closed Cases (E-Mc) (Reel 64FR)
- Region V: Cleveland: Closed Cases (N-Sh) (Reel 65FR)
- Region V: Cleveland: Closed Cases (Si-Z) (Reel 66FR)
- Region V: Cincinnati: Closed Cases (A-S) (Reel 67FR)
- Region V: Cincinnati: Closed Cases (T-Z) And Michigan: Non-docket able Cases (a-z) And Ohio: Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 68FRA)
- Region V: Cincinnati: Closed Cases (T-Z) And Michigan: Non-docket able Cases (a-z) And Ohio: Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 68FRB)
- Region VI: Administrative Files (A-S) (Reel 69FR)
- Region VI: Administrative Files (T-Z) And Administrative Correspondence, Organizational Contacts (A-I) (Reel 70FR)
- Region VI: Administrative Correspondence, Organizational Contacts (M-Z) (Reel 71FR)
- Region VI: Active Cases: Unions (A-Z) And Government Agencies (A-J) (Reel 72FR)
- Region VI: Active Cases: Government Agencies (K-Z) (Reel 73FRA)
- Region VI: Active Cases: Government Agencies (K-Z) (Reel 73FRB)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (A-B) (Reel 74FRA)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (A-B) (Reel 74FRB)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (C-Da) (Reel 75FRA)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (C-Da) (Reel 75FRB)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (De-H) (Reel 76FR)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (I-O) (Reel 77FRA)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (I-O) (Reel 77FRB)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (P-T) (Reel 78FRA)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (P-T) (Reel 78FRB)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (U-Z) And Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 79FRA)
- Region VI: Closed Cases (U-Z) And Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 79FRB)
- Region VII: Administrative Files (A-Z) (Reel 80FR)
- Region VII: Active Cases (A-Z) (Reel 81FR)
- Region VII: Closed Cases (A-Bo) (Reel 82FR)
- Region VII: Closed Cases (Br-F) (Reel 83FR)
- Region VII: Closed Cases (H-R) (Reel 84FR)
- Region VII: Closed Cases [S - U.S.E.S. (7-G-397)] (Reel 85FR)
- Region VII: Closed Cases [U.S.E.S. (7-G-20) -Z] And Non-docket able Cases (a-z) (Reel 86FR)
- Region VIII: Closed Cases (A-Z) (Reel 87FR)
- Region IX: Administrative Files (Reel 88FR)
  Telegrams, teletypes, telephone messages, weekly and monthly reports and Miscellaneous (Part I)
- Region IX: Administrative Files [Miscellaneous (Part II)] (Reel 89FR)
- Region IX: Active Cases: St. Louis (A-Z) And Kansas City (A-Z) And Closed Cases: St. Louis (A-C) (Reel 90FR)
- Region IX: St. Louis: Closed Cases (D-Z) (Reel 91FR)
- Region IX: Kansas City: Closed Cases (A-E) (Reel 92FR)
- Region IX: Kansas City: Closed Cases (F-N) (Reel 93FR)
- Region IX: Kansas City: Closed Cases (O-T) (Reel 94FR)
- Region IX: Kansas City: Closed Cases (U-Z) And Non-dock able Cases (Unarranged) (Reel 95FR)
- Region X, XII: Active Cases (Miscellaneous Cases From Arizona, New Mexico And Texas; Also A-Z) (Reel 96FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases (A-C) (Reel 97FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases (D-L) (Reel 98FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases (M-Pe) (Reel 99FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases (Ph-Se) (Reel 100FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases (Sh-T) (Reel 101FR)
- Region X Including XI, XIII: Closed Cases [(U-Z): Also Unarranged] (Reel 102FR)
- Region XII: Administrative Files, 1943-1945 (Reel 103FR)
  1943- 1944 (A-Z); 1945 (A-Z)
- Region XII: Administrative Files: Correspondence (Reel 104FR)
  Correspondence between Field Offices and Washington Headquarters (unarranged)
- Region XII: Administrative Files: Correspondence (Reel 105FR)
  Washington Office; WMC-FEPC Liaison; Civil Service Commission; Office files of Earl B. Dickerman; Complaints with memorandums (unarranged)
- Region XII: Los Angeles And San Francisco (Reel 106FR)
  Los Angeles Active Cases (A-Z); San Francisco Active Cases (A-Z) and No Action Recommended (A-Z)
- Region XII: Closed Cases (Reel 107FR)
  Referred to Washington Office (A-Z); Sent from Washington Office (A-Z)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (A-Bo) (Reel 108FR)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (Br-He) (Reel 109FR)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (Ho-Marine) (Reel 110FR)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (Marinship-Pl) (Reel 111FR)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (Po-Se) (Reel 112FR)
- Region XII: San Francisco: Closed Cases (Si-Z) (Reel 113FR)
- Region XII: Los Angeles: Closed Cases (A-Co) (Reel 114FR)
- Region XII: Los Angeles: Closed Cases (Cr-L) (Reel 115FR)
- Region XII: Los Angeles: Closed Cases (M-So) (Reel 116FR)
- Region XII: Los Angeles: Closed Cases (St-Z) And Non-docket able Cases (A-Z) (Reel 117FR)
  Pending Docketable Cases (unarranged)